<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Conor Lamb&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Conor Lamb&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:49:44 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://c0n0.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My personal blog&#39;s traffic is 95% AI crawlers this week</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/ai-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:32:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/ai-traffic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happened to check my analytics this week and saw this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Admittedly I don&amp;rsquo;t have much real traffic. I haven&amp;rsquo;t been writing much recently, but this irks me. And its super rude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not only is all my traffic fake, but its actively stealing my personality and voice. Potentially even cataloging me across my virtual profile. Like this is nothing new on the internet, but this is kind of egregious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll probably just fully block Singapore and Chinese IPs. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t sit great with me honestly, but I&amp;rsquo;d rather not be someone&amp;rsquo;s training data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Others&#39; AI PRs</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/reviewing-ai-prs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 13:31:43 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/reviewing-ai-prs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When you give me a PR to review, it should be complete and tested by YOU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should be proud and ready for your work to be shipped right now. I&amp;rsquo;m just here to double check things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should not be:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the first set of HUMAN eyes to look at your AI slop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;making your code DRY/maintainable because the AI didn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cleaning up the style/formatting to fit with the rest of our codebase because the AI didn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Next Project</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/my-next-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/my-next-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m optimizing my next product for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An eye popping headline (clicks)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As much conversations with users as humanly possible (pmf)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extra credit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s launched in a community interested in the topic, so the release post doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like an advertisement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfiltered Thoughts On A Failed Product Release</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/thoughts-after-releasing-modergator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:38:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/thoughts-after-releasing-modergator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I want to cover 2 things, before I get caught up in thought;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My feelings releasing &lt;a href=&#34;https://modergator.com&#34;&gt;modergator&lt;/a&gt; today and getting no new users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What to do next with modergator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;my-feelings-releasing-a-project-and-getting-no-users&#34;&gt;My feelings releasing a project and getting no users&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sucks. And its basically the worst outcome. And its what I expected to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our marketing plan was an after thought:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/SideProject/comments/1j9fpmh/modergator_an_api_for_small_dev_teams_to_moderate/&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on Reddit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.indiehackers.com/post/modergator-an-api-for-small-dev-teams-to-moderate-their-communities-5baff508f1&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on indie hackers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make a &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/modergator/status/1899826734205116828&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on twitter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the results, of course, are &lt;strong&gt;nothing&lt;/strong&gt;. Maybe 10 people came to our site.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chrome Debugger</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/dev-tip-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:31:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/dev-tip-chrome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You should use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.chrome.com/docs/devtools/javascript&#34;&gt;chrome debugger&lt;/a&gt; if you do any frontend js/ts work. /thread&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;console.log&lt;/code&gt; is dead. The debugger saves my ass every time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t need to set up anything&lt;/strong&gt; or even import it if your using Chrome. You just:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add &lt;code&gt;debugger;&lt;/code&gt; anywhere in your code: (stick it behind an &lt;code&gt;if&lt;/code&gt; if you like!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re debugging on the fly, find your file in the &lt;code&gt;sources&lt;/code&gt; tab and click &amp;ldquo;Add Breakpoint&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you can really debug all those god damn rerenders.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Make Waitlists For Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/why-wait-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:29:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/why-wait-lists/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-external-validation-for-a-new-idea&#34;&gt;1. External validation for a new idea&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the start of a project, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if only I have the problem I want to solve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more emails that join my wait list, the more excited people are about solving the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I try to be super straight up about who my product is for on the landing page. I also try to scope down the communicated project features as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 3hr Landing Page Build Strategy in 2025</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/speedrun-landingpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 13:52:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/speedrun-landingpage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I built a wait list landing page for a &lt;a href=&#34;https://modergator.com&#34;&gt;new project&lt;/a&gt; of mine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did it in around 2 hr 55 min. This is a PB for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I could definitely have done it faster, but with the trade offs I wanted, I am quite happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-strategy&#34;&gt;The Strategy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: I&amp;rsquo;m not affiliated with the brands mentioned.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-audit-current-state-of-drag-and-drop-website-builders&#34;&gt;1. Audit current state of drag-and-drop website builders&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time: 45 min | Cost: $0&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster PRs - Lower The Barrier Of Entry</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/faster-prs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:42:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/faster-prs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reviewing pull requests is a pain in the hole, but a necessary one. It is also massive time sync if you&amp;rsquo;re actually doing it right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;normal-pr-process&#34;&gt;Normal PR Process&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It often looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get slack message: “pwetty pwease review my PR :3 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/EpicGames/Signup/pull/24&#34;&gt;pr link&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open in browser, scroll through the code a bit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inner Monologue: “&lt;em&gt;This looks mostly understandable? Can I can get away without pulling this locally?&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decide to
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;run it locally&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stash current branch&amp;rsquo;s changes (&lt;em&gt;remember that you have a stash saved!&lt;/em&gt;). Pull down PR branch. Run the code/tests (Hopefully it runs). Click through all the changes going back and forth with the PR on github.com. See an issue in the editor and flip to the web browser, find the line, and post a comment in the PR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;view it in the browser&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attempt to read the code. &lt;em&gt;Optional&lt;/em&gt;: Try to “understand” the logic, but often you’re just &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/27810522/what-does-nit-mean-in-hacker-speak&#34;&gt;NITing&lt;/a&gt; formatting issues because you can’t run it. If you see a glaring issue or have a question, plop a comment in the PR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;yucky-dx&#34;&gt;Yucky DX&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a DX perspective, this process is slow and shit. If I think it’s slow and shit, I know my team does as well. If my team thinks it&amp;rsquo;s slow and shit, then when they’re stressed or lazy, they’re not pulling down my code, meaning they’re not reviewing my PRs well, meaning we&amp;rsquo;re often committing worse code and bugs into &lt;code&gt;master&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passing Thoughts Become Action</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/passing-thought-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:05:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/passing-thought-action/</guid>
      <description>Stopping and smelling the roses 🌹</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Getting Discovered</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/getting-discovered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/getting-discovered/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I blog sometimes. I publish a good bit of music as well, and yet, no one knows me.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This is fine. I happily mosey through life without internet celebrity, but candidly (and probably humanly), it would be nice to get recognition for the things that I make. So how does one get &amp;ldquo;discovered&amp;rdquo;?
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Youtube just recommended me this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Adz1G-LEu1g&#34;&gt;small linux youtuber&lt;/a&gt;, who struck me with a Jimmy Neutron style, brain blast on how these algorithms likely work.  In the video, he shows off his minimal youtube stats, and notices a parabolic uptick in his old linux videos views after he posts new videos with similar content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making A Language Learning Buddy w/ ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/chat-gpt-buddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/chat-gpt-buddy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m at a quietly frustrating point with my German language learning.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
It&amp;rsquo;s an uncomfortable expanse within A1-A2 levels where I pick up a myriad of words in a conversation, but I&amp;rsquo;m still not confident enough to say much. The usual solution here is one of brute force. Go make a fool of yourself, often and brazenly, in the wild. Talk to people around you, have awkward-as-hell conversations.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
But, how can I cash in on the ChatGPT hype that way?
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;strong&gt;cautiously&lt;/strong&gt; optimistic for ChatGPT. It really is amazing, the text responses it can generate are sometimes extremely nuanced and correct. But it&amp;rsquo;s also is not a silver bullet. Those touting it as the solution for everything may well end up relying on fancy Markov Chains and cause unimaginable damage.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
But for a semi-trivial thing like a basic language learning buddy, ChatGPT seems like an amazing solution! So here&amp;rsquo;s the results of my experiment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Small, Opinionated List of Nice Spots in Berlin</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-berlin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 14:49:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-berlin-guide/</guid>
      <description>My personal Berlin tourism list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make debugging suck less. Keep a logbook. 📓</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/make-debuggin-suck-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 09:16:09 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/make-debuggin-suck-less/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;scientists-keep-logbooks-for-their-findings-why-dont-computer-scientists&#34;&gt;Scientists keep logbooks for their findings. Why don&amp;rsquo;t computer scientists?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A great place to start doing this is for debugging. Debugging sucks enough as is, make it easier on yourself. A logbook will&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-enumerate-where-you-are-in-the-bug-fix-journey&#34;&gt;🗺 Enumerate where you are in the bug fix journey.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll forget this journey when you pick it up tomorrow, write it down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;-keep-you-rooted-to-the-ground-creating-an-issue-stack&#34;&gt;🌳 Keep you rooted to the ground. (Creating an &amp;ldquo;issue stack&amp;rdquo;.)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Related to above, it often feels like you&amp;rsquo;re completely lost in the aether when you&amp;rsquo;re 50 opened browser tabs deep into an issue that&amp;rsquo;s not even the same issue anymore, its a sub issue of a sub issue. &lt;em&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re in a stack of issues.&lt;/em&gt; But, if you have each issue written down, as you solve one, you can pop it off the stack and solve the next issue one at a time. Keeping this stack in your head sucks, and its easy to conflate understandings from this current problem with the previous problem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cool Junk That Conor Finds on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-cool-junk-he-found-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 19:52:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-cool-junk-he-found-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>My collection of things I find on my journeys through the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make a free resume website and blog in 10 min for programmers (or people unafraid of the command line)</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/website-in-10-minutes-for-programmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:27:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/website-in-10-minutes-for-programmers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;See the website you’re reading this on? I didn’t make this in 10 minutes…. But I sure could have if I had this tutorial. So here’s how you can make your own customizable resume website or blog for free in 2021 using the Hugo framework, a few commands in the terminal, Github Pages to host it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Skip to &lt;a href=&#34;#part-1-lets-make-your-website&#34;&gt;Part 1: Let’s make a website&lt;/a&gt; if you wanna skip my banter 😔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-off-why-hugo&#34;&gt;First off, Why &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I think it’s nifty as hell.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You basically only need to write &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.markdownguide.org/cheat-sheet/&#34;&gt;markdown&lt;/a&gt; once its set up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:27:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello World!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;❤️,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conor&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
