<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Conor Lamb&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://c0n0.com/categories/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on Conor Lamb&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.123.7</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 13:49:54 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://c0n0.com/categories/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Others&#39; AI PRs</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/reviewing-ai-prs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 13:31:43 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/reviewing-ai-prs/</guid>
      <description>When you give me a PR to review, it should be complete and tested by YOU.
You should be proud and ready for your work to be shipped right now. I&amp;rsquo;m just here to double check things.
I should not be:
the first set of HUMAN eyes to look at your AI slop making your code DRY/maintainable because the AI didn&amp;rsquo;t cleaning up the style/formatting to fit with the rest of our codebase because the AI didn&amp;rsquo;t The Bottom Line</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Next Project</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/my-next-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 20:13:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/my-next-project/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m optimizing my next product for:
An eye popping headline (clicks) As much conversations with users as humanly possible (pmf) Extra credit:
it&amp;rsquo;s launched in a community interested in the topic, so the release post doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like an advertisement </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfiltered Thoughts On A Failed Product Release</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/thoughts-after-releasing-modergator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:38:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/thoughts-after-releasing-modergator/</guid>
      <description>I want to cover 2 things, before I get caught up in thought;
My feelings releasing modergator today and getting no new users What to do next with modergator My feelings releasing a project and getting no users It sucks. And its basically the worst outcome. And its what I expected to happen.
Our marketing plan was an after thought:
Make a post on Reddit Make a post on indie hackers Make a post on twitter And the results, of course, are nothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Make Waitlists For Side Projects</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/why-wait-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:29:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/why-wait-lists/</guid>
      <description>1. External validation for a new idea At the start of a project, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if only I have the problem I want to solve.
The more emails that join my wait list, the more excited people are about solving the problem.
I try to be super straight up about who my product is for on the landing page. I also try to scope down the communicated project features as much as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 3hr Landing Page Build Strategy in 2025</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/speedrun-landingpage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 13:52:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/speedrun-landingpage/</guid>
      <description>Today I built a wait list landing page for a new project of mine.
I did it in around 2 hr 55 min. This is a PB for me.
I could definitely have done it faster, but with the trade offs I wanted, I am quite happy.
The Strategy Note: I&amp;rsquo;m not affiliated with the brands mentioned.
1. Audit current state of drag-and-drop website builders Time: 45 min | Cost: $0</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster PRs - Lower The Barrier Of Entry</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/faster-prs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:42:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/faster-prs/</guid>
      <description>Reviewing pull requests is a pain in the hole, but a necessary one. It is also massive time sync if you&amp;rsquo;re actually doing it right.
Normal PR Process It often looks like this:
Get slack message: “pwetty pwease review my PR :3 pr link” Open in browser, scroll through the code a bit Inner Monologue: “This looks mostly understandable? Can I can get away without pulling this locally?” Decide to run it locally Stash current branch&amp;rsquo;s changes (remember that you have a stash saved!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passing Thoughts Become Action</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/passing-thought-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:05:19 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/passing-thought-action/</guid>
      <description>Stopping and smelling the roses 🌹</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Getting Discovered</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/getting-discovered/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/getting-discovered/</guid>
      <description>I blog sometimes. I publish a good bit of music as well, and yet, no one knows me. This is fine. I happily mosey through life without internet celebrity, but candidly (and probably humanly), it would be nice to get recognition for the things that I make. So how does one get &amp;ldquo;discovered&amp;rdquo;? Youtube just recommended me this small linux youtuber, who struck me with a Jimmy Neutron style, brain blast on how these algorithms likely work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making A Language Learning Buddy w/ ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/chat-gpt-buddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/chat-gpt-buddy/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m at a quietly frustrating point with my German language learning. It&amp;rsquo;s an uncomfortable expanse within A1-A2 levels where I pick up a myriad of words in a conversation, but I&amp;rsquo;m still not confident enough to say much. The usual solution here is one of brute force. Go make a fool of yourself, often and brazenly, in the wild. Talk to people around you, have awkward-as-hell conversations. But, how can I cash in on the ChatGPT hype that way?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Small, Opinionated List of Nice Spots in Berlin</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-berlin-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 14:49:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-berlin-guide/</guid>
      <description>My personal Berlin tourism list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make debugging suck less. Keep a logbook. 📓</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/make-debuggin-suck-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 09:16:09 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/make-debuggin-suck-less/</guid>
      <description>Scientists keep logbooks for their findings. Why don&amp;rsquo;t computer scientists? A great place to start doing this is for debugging. Debugging sucks enough as is, make it easier on yourself. A logbook will&amp;hellip;
🗺 Enumerate where you are in the bug fix journey. You&amp;rsquo;ll forget this journey when you pick it up tomorrow, write it down.
🌳 Keep you rooted to the ground. (Creating an &amp;ldquo;issue stack&amp;rdquo;.) Related to above, it often feels like you&amp;rsquo;re completely lost in the aether when you&amp;rsquo;re 50 opened browser tabs deep into an issue that&amp;rsquo;s not even the same issue anymore, its a sub issue of a sub issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cool Junk That Conor Finds on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-cool-junk-he-found-on-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 19:52:31 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/conors-cool-junk-he-found-on-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>My collection of things I find on my journeys through the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make a free resume website and blog in 10 min for programmers (or people unafraid of the command line)</title>
      <link>https://c0n0.com/posts/website-in-10-minutes-for-programmers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:27:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://c0n0.com/posts/website-in-10-minutes-for-programmers/</guid>
      <description>See the website you’re reading this on? I didn’t make this in 10 minutes…. But I sure could have if I had this tutorial. So here’s how you can make your own customizable resume website or blog for free in 2021 using the Hugo framework, a few commands in the terminal, Github Pages to host it.
Skip to Part 1: Let’s make a website if you wanna skip my banter 😔</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
